https://www.bridgerbowl.com/privacy

What to Expect This Season
Photo by
Louise JohnsPersonal privacy, confidence, and trust in Bridger Bowl when visiting bridgerbowl.com is of utmost importance. No personal information is collected at this site unless provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an activity that asks for the information. Users of Bridger Bowl’s website are never under any obligation to provide personal information of any sort.Information Collection, Use, and SharingBridger Bowl only collects personal information necessary to provide information or services requested by an individual and is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. This policy only applies to information we collect on this Bridger Bowl website (“Site”) or in electronic messaging between you and Bridger Bowl. This policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including any other website operated by any third party that may link to or be accessible from or on this Site. Collected information is never sold or rented.Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site. By accessing or using this Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.Information collected by Bridger Bowl is used to respond appropriately to user requests or to improve the website. Information is never shared with any third party outside of Bridger Bowl other than as necessary to fulfill a request (e.g. ship an order), unless required by government or law enforcement with the need to know by a proper authority.Unless asked not to, contact may be made via email in the future for notification of specials, snow alerts, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Children Under the Age of 13 NoticeOur Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. No one under the age of 18 should use this site. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification or parental consent, we will delete that information. California residents under 16 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their personal information.How We Use Your InformationWe use information that we collect about you and provide to us, including any personal information:For Registration and Purchases as described below.To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.To improve the services we provide as part of our business purpose.To carry out our obligations and legal basis, as well as, enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including processing payments and delivery of services and purchased items.To notify you about changes to our Site or any services or products we offer or provide through the Site.To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.In any other way may describe when you provide the information.For any other purpose with your consent.You may send us an email to request acces to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting any applicable login account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.RegistrationIn order to register for services (e.g. events, lessons, passes, lodging, etc.), a user must first complete an account registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact users about the products/services on the site in which interest has been expressed such as weather or snow conditions. In some cases, a user may be required to provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about themselves, but it is not required.PurchasesWhen purchasing passes, gifts, lessons, or gift cards online, users will be asked to provide credit card account information. In order to make a purchase, contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date) will be required. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill orders. Account information is only used to authorize the purchase and is never stored on Bridger Bowl's systems. If trouble is encountered processing an order, Bridger Bowl will use this information to contact the user to finalize the request.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time information via surveys or contests may be requested. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and users may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information may be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.SecurityBridger Bowl is committed to the security of information collected. We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. When sensitive information is submitted via email or the website, user information is protected both online and offline.While encryption is used to protect sensitive information transmitted online, information is also protected offline. Only employees needing the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which personally identifiable information is stored are maintained in a secure environment.Retention of InformationRecords needed to support Bridger Bowl's operations and functions are retained, managed, and accessible in electronic record keeping or filing systems. Records transmitted to this site will be identified, managed, protected, and retained as long as needed to meet historical, administrative, fiscal, or legal requirements.CookiesBridger Bowl uses "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help improve user access to the site and simplify the browsing experience. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. For instance, when a cookie is used, a user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the site. Cookies can also enable targeting the interests of users to enhance the experience on the site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on the site and can be viewed and deleted in a browser application, if desired.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Bridger Bowl is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. Users are encouraged to be aware when leaving this site to read the privacy statements of any other site.Changes to Our Privacy PolicyIt is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Site.Request for Removal of InformationUsers of bridgerbowl.com may opt out of any future contact at any time by contacting support via the email address provided on this website. The removal of such information will affect the ability of Bridger Bowl to communicate with a user and may also require future entry of such information when purchasing goods or services from Bridger Bowl.Contact UsTo ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:webmaster@bridgerbowl.com
Bridger Bowl, Inc.
15795 Bridger Canyon Dr.
Bozeman, MT 59715
United States
Phone:
(406) 587-2111BRIDGERBOWLSKITHECOLDSMOKEEST.1955B
OZEMAN,MTSki & RideMountainWeatherLessonsGearEventsMediaAccount
Account
Ski & RidePasses & TicketsReservationsPass BenefitsBuy a GiftMountainMountain InfoTrail MapSkier ServicesSustainabilityHistorySummer ActivitiesGetting HereBozemanXC SkiingWeatherSnow ReportWebcamsGrooming ReportLive WeatherTablesLessonsPrivate LessonsMax3 Group LessonsAdaptive ProgramsGearRentalsTuning & RepairRetail StoreEventsAll EventsMediaVideo Library
